<?xml version="1.0"?><PPGallery>	<item>		<title>Busta Rhymes</title>		<thumb>asset/photo/small3.jpg</thumb>		<full>asset/photo/full3.jpg</full>		<caption>When Disaster Strikes</caption>		<recording>Elektra/Flipmode</recording>		<description>Busta Rhymes opens his second album with a ridiculous monologue predicting global destruction before the year 2000. The only thing in danger of vaporizing over the next two years is Rhymes's career. Listening to Busta's gruff voice for well over an hour is an endurance test of the highest order, especially after MTV and radio have relentlessly subjected listeners to his "Woo-haa!" battle cry. Thankfully, Busta makes his pipes contort in every way possible on When Disaster Strikes... From mellow to wild, over an eclectic mix of samples that range from Seals and Croft to KC and the Sunshine Band to Henri Mancini. Sean "Puffy" Combs produces a track called "The Body Rock" that sounds like an old-school Tribe Called Quest cut, while Erykah Badu helps Busta forget the rampant sexism and violence for a minute as the unlikely duo gets spiritual on "One." Disaster avoided...for now.</description>		<track_list>				<track>					<number>1</number>					<title>Intro</title>					<time>3:19</time>					<url>music/Busta/1.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>2</number>					<title>The Whole World Lookin' At Me</title>					<time>2:32</time>					<url>music/Busta/2.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>3</number>					<title>Survival Hungry</title>					<time>3:08</time>					<url>music/Busta/3.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>4</number>					<title>When Disaster Strikes</title>					<time>7:39</time>					<url>music/Busta/4.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>5</number>					<title>So Hardcore</title>					<time>3:32</time>					<url>music/Busta/5.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>6</number>					<title>Turn It Up</title>					<time>3:39</time>					<url>music/Busta/6.mp3</url>				</track>		</track_list>	</item>	<item>		<title>Common</title>		<thumb>asset/photo/small9.jpg</thumb>		<full>asset/photo/full9.jpg</full>		<caption>Be</caption>		<recording>GOOD/Geffen/Imani Records</recording>		<description>Two albums and out. Be was touted as Common's comeback album after the commercially disastrous Electric Circus. His previous album lacked promotion following MCA Records's absorption under Geffen. His new alliance with Kanye West helped to spark public interest in the project, as the album was produced by West and released by his own label G.O.O.D. Music. Nas's debut album Illmatic was the biggest influence on Be[citation needed]. The results show that Common was clearly aware, and perhaps agreeing, with the negative criticisms about Electric Circus. In comparison to that album, Be is lean, immediate, and commanding, yet also restrained in its musical ambitions. Many believe it to be his safest album. Of the reaction to the album, the rapper said: "I don't think Electric Circus was as focused. Though I'd done some progressive hip-hop, people know me as the b-boy. When I showed them something different, a different style of b-boy, there were like, "Hold up. You can be Afrocentric, but what's this rock shit that you're doing?"[2] Many of the beats created by West, and which Common rejected for the project, later appeared on West's studio album Late Registration.</description>		<track_list>				<track>					<number>1</number>					<title>BE</title>					<time>4:23</time>					<url>music/Be/1.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>2</number>					<title>The Corner</title>					<time>4:23</time>					<url>music/Be/2.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>3</number>					<title>Go</title>					<time>4:30</time>					<url>music/Be/3.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>4</number>					<title>Faithful</title>					<time>4:08</time>					<url>music/Be/4.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>5</number>					<title>Testify</title>					<time>4:29</time>					<url>music/Be/5.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>6</number>					<title>Love Is...</title>					<time>4:01</time>					<url>music/Be/6.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>7</number>					<title>Chi City</title>					<time>4:01</time>					<url>music/Be/7.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>9</number>					<title>Real People</title>					<time>4:01</time>					<url>music/Be/9.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>10</number>					<title>They Say</title>					<time>4:01</time>					<url>music/Be/10.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>11</number>					<title>It's Your World</title>					<time>4:01</time>					<url>music/Be/11.mp3</url>				</track>		</track_list>	</item>	<item>		<title>Dr. Dre</title>		<thumb>asset/photo/small7.jpg</thumb>		<full>asset/photo/full7.jpg</full>		<caption>The Chronic</caption>		<recording>Death Row/Interscope Records</recording>		<description>				The Chronic is the solo debut studio album of hip hop producer and rapper Dr. Dre, released December 15, 1992 on his former own label, Death Row Records, and distributed by Priority Records. The album was named after a slang term for high-grade cannabis. The album cover is an homage to Zig-Zag rolling papers. The Chronic was recorded by Dr. Dre following his departure from N.W.A and Ruthless Records over a financial dispute, and consequently featured both subtle and direct insults at Ruthless and its owner, former N.W.A group member, Eazy-E.		Dr. Dre's production is noted for founding and popularizing the G-funk sub-genre within gangsta rap. The album peaked at number three on the Billboard 200 and has sold over three million copies, which led to him becoming one of the top ten best-selling American performing artists of 1993. It is widely regarded as one of the most important and influential albums of the 1990s and regarded by many fans and peers to be the most well-produced hip-hop album of all time.				</description>		<track_list>				<track>					<number>1</number>					<title>Lolo</title>					<time>1:57</time>					<url>music/2001/1.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>2</number>					<title>The Watcher</title>					<time>4:52</time>					<url>music/2001/2.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>3</number>					<title>F*** You</title>					<time>4:21</time>					<url>music/2001/3.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>4</number>					<title>Still D.R.E</title>					<time>4:33</time>					<url>music/2001/4.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>5</number>					<title>Big Ego's</title>					<time>3:58</time>					<url>music/2001/5.mp3</url>				</track>		</track_list>	</item>	<item>		<title>T.I.</title>		<thumb>asset/photo/small11.jpg</thumb>		<full>asset/photo/full11.jpg</full>		<caption>Paper Trail</caption>		<recording>Grand Hustle/Atlantic Records</recording>		<description>On November 13, 2007, while awaiting trial for federal weapons charges against him, T.I. announced he had been writing songs for a new album to be entitled Paper Trail. He wrote his lyrics down on paper, which he had not done since his debut album, I'm Serious.[2] The album highlights his "fear, anger and guilt" as he awaited trial.[3]The album was scheduled to be released in September 2008, but was subsequently moved up to an August 12 after the release of the promotional and lead single "No Matter What" and high demand of the album. At the time, T.I. said that the first single may have been "Top of the World", originally featuring B.o.B and Kanye West, explaining that the song was "a reflective song about our humble beginnings and how far we've come".[4] The album was pushed back for a release date of September 2, then September 9 and to its final release date of September 30, 2008.[5]T.I. confirmed that Rihanna, Justin Timberlake, Usher and John Legend were set to appear on the album in August 2008.[6] Other confirmed guests were B.o.B, Kanye West, Jay-Z, Lil Wayne, Ludacris and Swizz Beatz. The album was produced by DJ Toomp, Drumma Boy, and Just Blaze, as well as Danja, Jim Jonsin, Kanye West and Swizz Beatz.</description>		<track_list>				<track>					<number>1</number>					<title>56 Bars</title>					<time>3:02</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/1.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>2</number>					<title>I'm Illy</title>					<time>5:39</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/2.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>3</number>					<title>Ready for Whatever</title>					<time>5:39</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/3.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>4</number>					<title>On Top of the World</title>					<time>5:39</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/4.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>5</number>					<title>Live Your Life [ft. Rihanna]</title>					<time>5:39</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/5.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>6</number>					<title>Whatever You Like</title>					<time>4:10</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/6.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>7</number>					<title>No Matter What</title>					<time>4:10</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/7.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>8</number>					<title>My LIfe, Your Entertainment</title>					<time>4:10</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/8.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>9</number>					<title>Porn Star</title>					<time>4:10</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/9.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>10</number>					<title>Swing Ya Rag</title>					<time>4:10</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/10.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>11</number>					<title>What's Up, What's Haapenin'</title>					<time>5:01</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/11.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>12</number>					<title>Every Chance I Get</title>					<time>5:01</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/12.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>13</number>					<title>Swagga Like Us [ft. Kanye West, Jay-Z and Li'l Wayne]</title>					<time>5:28</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/13.mp3</url>				</track>				<track>					<number>14</number>					<title>Slide Show[ft. John Legend]</title>					<time>5:28</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/14.mp3</url>				</track><track>					<number>15</number>					<title>You Ain't Missin' Nothing</title>					<time>5:28</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/15.mp3</url>				</track><track>					<number>16</number>					<title>Dead And Gone [ft. Justin Timemberlanke]</title>					<time>5:28</time>					<url>music/Paper_Trail/16.mp3</url>				</track>		</track_list>	</item></PPGallery>