<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<manual>
	<item>
		<title>Destiny's Child : Soldier [ft. Li'l Wayne &#38; T.I.]</title>
		<asset>asset/photo/6.png</asset>
		<promo>"Soldier" produced by Knowles and Harrison and released as the album's second single in fall 2004. The song was also performed by Beyoncé on the Beyoncé Experience tour. It was performed as a remix in a Destiny's Child medley. The remix contained a sample of the Soulja Boy Tell 'Em's "Crank That (Soulja Boy)."

"Soldier" peaked at number 1 in Canada and Denmark and number 3 in the United States, where it became the group's ninth and final consecutive top hit, number 4 in the UK, which makes T.I.'s &#38; Lil Wayne's first top 5 hit in the UK and peaked within the top 5 in New Zealand, Denmark, Ireland, Israel, Finland, Italy, Greece and Switzerland. The song also was nominated for a Grammy Award for Best Rap/Sung Collaboration category and won the group a Soul Train Lady of Soul Award for Best R&#38;B/Soul Single by a Group, Band or Duo. The song was sampled for "Grillz" by Nelly, Paul Wall, and Ali &#38; Gipp. This was also sampled for the song "Body Marked Up" by Willy Northpole.
		</promo>
		<recording>Destiny's Child</recording>
		<caption>videos/12.flv</caption>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Jay-Z : Roc Boys</title>
		<asset>asset/photo/1.png</asset>
		<promo>The music video was directed by Chris Robinson.  The video was shot in New York City in Jay-Z's The 40/40 Club.

The intro of the video contains the chorus from Hello Brooklyn 2.0. The video features cameo appearances by Rick Ross, Memphis Bleek, Diddy, Freeway, Nas, Terrence J, Tru Life, Young Gunz, Jadakiss, Swizz Beatz, Drew Sidora, Kristia Krueger, Chain 4, Chantel, Beanie Sigel, Cassie, DJ Clue, Larry Johnson, Tristan Wilds, Just Blaze, Tru life, Zab Judah, The-Dream, Irv Gotti and Mariah Carey. Kanye West is not featured in the video because of a scheduling conflict, at the time he was on tour in Dubai, as posted in his blog.

The young Jay-Z was portrayed by actor Samgoma Edwards. Director Chris Robinson personally sought out Edwards for the role after Edwards and his older brother Samtubia and friend Chris Alvarez shot their own video project titled "The Young Hov Project", based on tracks from Jay-Z's The Black Album.</promo>
		<recording>Jay-Z</recording>
		<caption>videos/7.flv</caption>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Justin Timberlake : What Goes Around Comes Back Around</title>
		<asset>asset/photo/5.png</asset>
		<promo>"What Goes Around.../...Comes Around" is a pop-R&#38;B song performed in a slow manner.  It is composed in the key  of A dorian, in common time. With a gentle and midtempo beat,  the tempo is pacing to seventy-two beats per minute.  The song features a two-minute interlude  titled "Comes Around", featuring the album's producer Timbaland, spanning to a seven minutes and twenty-eight-second track. Timberlake's voice ranges from B3 to C6.  Musically, the song is similar to the type of music produced on Timberlake's Justified album; however, it is the only link from FutureSex/LoveSounds to Justified.

In the beginning of the song, there is a five-second harmony line of two bağlamas (one each panned far left and far right on respect octaves), a Greek folk instrument. The beat is then changed to a more upbeat version of the same melody with more percussion. Timbaland used the oud to mellow out the guitar riff. The chord series follows the Am-C-G-D keys. Following the instrumental, Timberlake begins the verse at thirteenth bar. The original track had a bridge, including the pre-verses, the verses and the choruses. After hearing the vocals of Timberlake, they decided to remove the bridge and follow a simple flow, because they felt its "too much" to have it and a break at the end of the song. Timbaland provides backing vocals on the song.
		</promo>
		<recording>Justin Timberlake</recording>
		<caption>videos/11.flv</caption>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lady Gaga : Poker Face</title>
		<asset>asset/photo/9.png</asset>
		<promo>The music video for "Poker Face", directed by Ray Kay and aided by Anthony Mandler,  was filmed at the luxury villa on bwin PokerIsland.  bwin also provided the poker equipment and obtained product placements in return.  The video premiered on October 22, 2008. It is set by a pool, as well as in a mansion. It begins with Gaga emerging out of the pool wearing a shiny masquerade mask and a black full-body leotard, with two Great Danes beside her (Lava and her son Rumpus). She throws the mask aside and the song begins with a facial shot of Gaga singing it.  Gaga wears a metallic sticker on her left cheek in this shot. Featured in the video are scenes of Gaga in a mansion and dancing poolside with her dancers in a turquoise leotard.  Gaga attends a wild party where every man and woman tries their luck on a strip poker game. The party gets wilder when all the party's guests strip down to their underwear, dance around, and share kisses with each other. The video also features two harlequin  Great Danes and several white mannequins on her swimming pool deck. During the musical interlude before the "I won't tell you that I love you" hook, Gaga is shown in her trademark "Pop Music Will Never Be Low Brow" sunglasses while sitting beside the pool. The video ends with the head shot of Gaga singing the Mum-mum-mum-ma hook.</promo>
		<recording>Lady Gaga</recording>
		<caption>videos/15.flv</caption>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Taylor Swift : You Belong With Me</title>
		<asset>asset/photo/8.png</asset>
		<promo>"You Belong With Me" is a song in which the young protagonist, singing in first person, has intense romantic feelings for a male friend who is involved with another woman.

Swift commented about the song's background: "I came into the writing session with Liz Rose and said... "I've got this idea. I had overheard a friend of mine talking to his girlfriend and he was completely on the defensive saying, 'No, baby... I had to get off the phone really quickly... I tried to call you right back... Of course I love you. More than anything!</promo>
		<recording>Taylor Swift</recording>
		<caption>videos/14.flv</caption>
	</item>
</manual>
